arofanatics.com 2004-12-09

# Arofanatics.com - Arowana Community for Aro collectors around the World!

**Arofanatics.com Privacy Policy Statement**

This is the privacy policy of Arofanatics.com.   
We can be reached via e-mail at alvin@dinotoons.com 

**Visitor logs**   
For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes and logs the comsumer's domain name / IP address, as well as the time of access in the raw server log files. The infomation is automatically generate in to a usage statistics based on the number of visitors. The Web server provider may use these infomation for debugging purposes as well as to detect fraud - for the safety of its consumers. 

**Registration Infomation**

We do not require explicit registration to browse or read the contents on our webpage. Registration is only required for those who would like to participate in the forums or to create their own gallery pages. 

We collect the e-mail addresses of those who post messages to our bulletin board, the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail, information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information and/or site registrations. The emails are required to validify the identity of the users. These infomation are kept strictly confidential and not released to any party unless approved by the consumers themselves. We allow consumers to hide their email from view via their own control panel in the bulletin board. 

The information we collect is not shared with other organizations for commercial purposes. 

**Cookies**

With respect to cookies: We use cookies to store visitors preferences, record past activity at a site in order to provide better service when visitors return to our site , customize Web page content based on visitors' browser type or other information that the visitor sends. 

Cookies are used to verify whether a consumer has access to restricted pages that only they have access to. Such pages includes the gallery as well as bulletin board users' control panel. The usage of cookies can be turned off via the bulletin board users' control panel. 

**Privacy Policy Changes**

From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site at Arofanatics.com periodically. 

Upon request we offer visitors the ability to have inaccuracies corrected in contact information, unique identifiers, communications that the consumer/visitor has directed to Arofanatics.com. 

Consumers can have this information corrected by sending us e-mail at the above address. 

**Advertising Privacy**

This website receives advertising from BURST! Media advertising network. Demographical data is collected when visitors fill up the voluntary survey that collects only data required to form a demographical model. No information will be used to contact visitors as anonymity is ensured. For more information of BURST! Media's privacy policies, please visit http://www.burstmedia.com/release/privacy.asp for more information. 

This website receives advertising from the CMG Enterprises network. For more information on what data is collected from Internet consumers through CMG Enterprises ads please see their privacy policy statement at http://cmgenterprise.com/policy.htm

We also receive from time to time, pop-under advertisements from the Everyone.net limited to no more than 3 times per day per user within a 24 hour period. Please review their privacy policy statement at http://www.everyone.net/main/html/p_policy.html 

**Security**

With respect to security: We have appropriate security measures in place at the physical facilities of our web service provider to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at Arofanatics.com. 

If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact the local consumer protection office.
